

# JUSTYNA TOMCZYK

# Front-end developer

PORTFOLIO: http://www.tomczykjustyna.pl/

Email: tomczykjustyna99@gmail.com

Phone: +48 530 298 458

Date of birth: October 7, 1999

City: Cracow

I graduated from Informatics and Econometrics at AGH University of Science and Technology in Krakow, where I gained knowledge in programming and data analysis. Since June 2023, I have been working as a front-end developer, specializing in creating online stores using the Shoper platform. I am a creative and ambitious person who loves learning new things and embracing challenges.

### **SKILLS**

HTML5 / CSS3 / JavaScript / ReactJS / jQuery / Shoper / Smarty / Bootstrap / Sass / RWD / Git / analytical thinking / teamwork

#### **MY PROJECTS**

GitHub: https://github.com/JustynaTomczyk7

- Portfolio: http://www.tomczykjustyna.pl/ HTML, Sass
- e-Flowers ReactJS, TypeScript, Local Storage
- Ultimate-App TypeScript
- Weather application JavaScript, OpenWeather API
- Music Player JavaScript
- Furniture Shop Sass, JavaScript
- to-do-list JavaScript, Local Storage
- Saasify HTML, CSS
- https://www.plytkarze.com/ Bootstrap

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

06/2023 - Present Front-end developer (Mamezi Studio Jakub Ogórek)

implementing store templates, creating modules and features in JavaScript, ongoing maintenance of operating stores, optimizing store speed for Google

Page Speed Insights

04/2019 - 12/2021 **Office worker** (CallPage sp. z o.o.)

managing payments, organizing and storing company documents, contacting

external suppliers, and maintaining employee records

**EDUCATION** 

2019 - 2022 AGH University of Science and Technology in Krakow

Bachelor of Informatics and Econometrics

2015 - 2019 **ZSE 1 in Krakow** 

Profession: Economic Technician

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).